<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Arraykart</string>
    <string name="title_activity_home_navigation">HomeNavigationActivity</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_header_title">User Name</string>
    <string name="nav_header_subtitle">user.name@gmail.com</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="menu_home">Home</string>
    <string name="menu_gallery">Categories</string>
    <string name="menu_slideshow">Orders</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>

    <string name="facebook_app_id">1594258097572065</string>
    <string name="fb_login_protocol_scheme">fb1594258097572065</string>
    <string name="phoneNumber">+919311900912</string>
    <string name="eMail">yourfriends@arraykart.com</string>
    <string name="further_queries">For further queries, contact us through:</string>
    <string name="title_activity_community">CommunityActivity</string>
    <!-- Strings used for fragments for navigation -->
    <string name="first_fragment_label">First Fragment</string>
    <string name="second_fragment_label">Second Fragment</string>
    <string name="next">Next</string>
    <string name="previous">Previous</string>

    <string name="hello_first_fragment">Hello first fragment</string>
    <string name="hello_second_fragment">Hello second fragment. Arg: %1$s</string>
    <string name="help_center">Help Center</string>
    <string name="community">Community Buying</string>
    <string name="name">Name</string>
    <string name="register">Register</string>
    <string name="aadhaar">Aadhaar</string>
    <string name="enter_aadhaar_no">Enter aadhaar No</string>
    <string name="enter_your_name">Enter your name</string>
    <string name="register_to_become_a_community_head">Register to become a Community Head</string>
    <string name="skip">Skip</string>
    <string name="edit_address">Edit Address</string>
    <string name="city">City*</string>
    <string name="locality_area_or_street">Locality, area or street*</string>
    <string name="flat_no_or_building_name">Flat no. or Building name*</string>
    <string name="pincode">Pincode*</string>
    <string name="state">state*</string>
    <string name="fullname">FullName*</string>
    <string name="mobile_no">Mobile no.*</string>
    <string name="alternative_mobile_no_optional">Alternative Mobile no(optional).*</string>
    <string name="update_your_address">update your address</string>
    <string name="add_new_address">Add new address</string>
    <string name="address_form">Address Form</string>
    <string name="reviews">Reviews</string>
    <string name="user_has_been_already_registered">User Has Been Already Registered!</string>
    <string name="search_arraykart">Search Arraykart.in</string>
    <string name="rs_30000">RS.30000/-</string>
    <string name="total_amount">Total Amount</string>
    <string name="continue_string">continue</string>
    <string name="cost_kg">cost/kg</string>
    <string name="_1kg_200">1Kg/200</string>
    <string name="_2kg_400">2kg/400</string>
    <string name="_3kg_600">3Kg/600</string>
    <string name="_4kg_800">4Kg/800</string>
    <string name="_5kg_1000">5kg/1000</string>
    <string name="cost">cost</string>
    <string name="_100_200">100–200</string>
    <string name="_200_300">200–300</string>
    <string name="_300_400">300–400</string>
    <string name="upto_500">upto 500</string>
    <string name="_500">500</string>
    <string name="search">search</string>
    <string name="overview">OVERVIEW</string>
    <string name="overview_content_1">This Application is operated by Arraykart Techable Private Limited. Throughout the Application, the terms “we”, “us” and “our” refer to Arraykart Techable Private Limited. Arraykart Techable Private Limited offers this Application, including all information, tools and services available from this Application to you, the user, conditioned upon your acceptance of all terms, conditions, policies and notices stated here.</string>
    <string name="overview_content_2">By visiting our Application and/ or purchasing something from us, you engage in our “Service” and agree to be bound by the following terms and conditions (“Terms of Service”, “Terms”), including those additional terms and conditions and policies referenced herein and/or available by hyperlink. These Terms of Service apply to all users of the Application, including without limitation users who are browsers, vendors, customers, merchants, and/ or contributors of content.</string>
    <string name="overview_content_3">Please read these Terms of Service carefully before accessing or using our Application. By accessing or using any part of the Application, you agree to be bound by these Terms of Service. If you do not agree to all the terms and conditions of this agreement, then you may not access the Application or use any services. If these Terms of Service are considered an offer, acceptance is expressly limited to these Terms of Service.</string>
    <string name="overview_content_4">Any new features or tools which are added to the current store shall also be subject to the Terms of Service. You can review the most current version of the Terms of Service at any time on this page. We reserve the right to update, change or replace any part of these Terms of Service by posting updates and/or changes to our Application. It is your responsibility to check this page periodically for changes. Your continued use of or access to the Application following the posting of any changes constitutes acceptance of those changes.</string>
    <string name="ov_section1">SECTION 1 - ONLINE STORE TERMS</string>
    <string name="ov_section1_content1">By agreeing to these Terms of Service, you represent that you are at least the age of majority in your state or province of residence, or that you are the age of majority in your state or province of residence and you have given us your consent to allow any of your minor dependents to use this Application.</string>
    <string name="ov_section1_content2">You may not use our products for any illegal or unauthorized purpose nor may you, in the use of the Service, violate any laws in your jurisdiction (including but not limited to copyright laws).You must not transmit any worms or viruses or any code of a destructive nature.A breach or violation of any of the Terms will result in an immediate termination of your Services.</string>
    <string name="ov_section2">SECTION 2 - GENERAL CONDITIONS</string>
    <string name="ov_section2_content1">We reserve the right to refuse service to anyone for any reason at any time.You understand that your content (not including credit card information), may be transferred unencrypted and involve (a) transmissions over various networks; and (b) changes to conform and adapt to technical requirements of connecting networks or devices. Credit card information is always encrypted during transfer over networks.</string>
    <string name="ov_section2_content2">You agree not to reproduce, duplicate, copy, sell, resell or exploit any portion of the Service, use of the Service, or access to the Service or any contact on the Application through which the service is provided, without express written permission by us.</string>
    <string name="ov_section2_content3">The headings used in this agreement are included for convenience only and will not limit or otherwise affect these Terms.</string>
    <string name="ov_section3">SECTION 3 - ACCURACY, COMPLETENESS AND TIMELINESS OF INFORMATION</string>
    <string name="ov_section3_content1">We are not responsible if information made available on this Application is not accurate, complete or current. The material on this Application is provided for general information only and should not be relied upon or used as the sole basis for making decisions without consulting primary, more accurate, more complete or more timely sources of information. Any reliance on the material on this Application is at your own risk.</string>
    <string name="ov_section3_content2">This Application may contain certain historical information. Historical information, necessarily, is not current and is provided for your reference only. We reserve the right to modify the contents of this Application at any time, but we have no obligation to update any information on our Application. You agree that it is your responsibility to monitor changes to our Application.</string>
    <string name="ov_section4">SECTION 4 - MODIFICATIONS TO THE SERVICE AND PRICES</string>
    <string name="ov_section4_content1">Prices for our products are subject to change without notice.</string>
    <string name="ov_section4_content2">We reserve the right at any time to modify or discontinue the Service (or any part or content thereof) without notice at any time.</string>
    <string name="ov_section4_content3">We shall not be liable to you or to any third-party for any modification, price change, suspension or discontinuance of the Service.</string>
    <string name="ov_section5">SECTION 5 - PRODUCTS OR SERVICES (if applicable)</string>
    <string name="ov_section5_content1">Certain products or services may be available exclusively online through the Application. These products or services may have limited quantities and are subject to return or exchange only according to our Return Policy.</string>
    <string name="ov_section5_content2">We have made every effort to display as accurately as possible the colors and images of our products that appear at the store. We cannot guarantee that your computer monitor\'s display of any color will be accurate.</string>
    <string name="ov_section5_content3">We reserve the right, but are not obligated, to limit the sales of our products or Services to any person, geographic region or jurisdiction. We may exercise this right on a case-by-case basis. We reserve the right to limit the quantities of any products or services that we offer. All descriptions of products or product pricing are subject to change at anytime without notice, at the sole discretion of us. We reserve the right to discontinue any product at any time. Any offer for any product or service made on this Application is void where prohibited.</string>
    <string name="ov_section5_content4">We do not warrant that the quality of any products, services, information, or other material purchased or obtained by you will meet your expectations, or that any errors in the Service will be corrected.</string>
    <string name="ov_section6">SECTION 6 - ACCURACY OF BILLING AND ACCOUNT INFORMATION</string>
    <string name="ov_section6_content2">We reserve the right to refuse any order you place with us. We may, in our sole discretion, limit or cancel quantities purchased per person, per household or per order. These restrictions may include orders placed by or under the same customer account, the same credit card, and/or orders that use the same billing and/or shipping address. In the event that we make a change to or cancel an order, we may attempt to notify you by contacting the e-mail and/or billing address/phone number provided at the time the order was made. We reserve the right to limit or prohibit orders that, in our sole judgment, appear to be placed by dealers, resellers or distributors.</string>
    <string name="ov_section6_content3">You agree to provide current, complete and accurate purchase and account information for all purchases made at our store. You agree to promptly update your account and other information, including your email address so that we can complete your transactions and contact you as needed. For more detail, please review our Returns Policy.</string>
    <string name="ov_section7">SECTION 7 - OPTIONAL TOOLS</string>
    <string name="ov_section7_content1">We may provide you with access to third-party tools over which we neither monitor nor have any control nor input. You acknowledge and agree that we provide access to such tools ”as is” and “as available” without any warranties, representations or conditions of any kind and without any endorsement. We shall have no liability whatsoever arising from or relating to your use of optional third-party tools.</string>
    <string name="ov_section7_content2">Any use by you of optional tools offered through the Application is entirely at your own risk and discretion and you should ensure that you are familiar with and approve of the terms on which tools are provided by the relevant third-party provider(s).</string>
    <string name="ov_section7_content3">We may also, in the future, offer new services and/or features through the Application (including, the release of new tools and resources). Such new features and/or services shall also be subject to these Terms of Service.</string>
    <string name="ov_section8">SECTION 8 - THIRD-PARTY LINKS</string>
    <string name="ov_section8_content1">Certain content, products and services available via our Service may include materials from third parties.</string>
    <string name="ov_section8_content2">Third-party links on this Application may direct you to third-party Applications that are not affiliated with us. We are not responsible for examining or evaluating the content or accuracy and we do not warrant and will not have any liability or responsibility for any third-party materials or Applications, or for any other materials, products, or services of third-parties.</string>
    <string name="ov_section8_content3">We are not liable for any harm or damages related to the purchase or use of goods, services, resources, content, or any other transactions made in connection with any third-party Applications. Please review carefully the third-party\'s policies and practices and make sure you understand them before you engage in any transaction. Complaints, claims, concerns, or questions regarding third party products should be directed to the third-party.</string>
    <string name="ov_section9">SECTION 9 - USER COMMENTS, FEEDBACK AND OTHER SUBMISSIONS</string>
    <string name="ov_section9_content1">If, at our request, you send certain specific submissions (for example contest entries) or without a request from us you send creative ideas, suggestions, proposals, plans, or other materials, whether online, by email, by postal mail, or otherwise (collectively, \'comments\'), you agree that we may, at any time, without restriction, edit, copy, publish, distribute, translate and otherwise use in any medium any comments that you forward to us. We are and shall be under no obligation (1) to maintain any comments in confidence; (2) to pay compensation for any comments; or (3) to respond to any comments.</string>
    <string name="ov_section9_content2">We may, but have no obligation to, monitor, edit or remove content that we determine in our sole discretion are unlawful, offensive, threatening, libelous, defamatory, pornographic, obscene or otherwise objectionable or violates any party’s intellectual property or these Terms of Service.</string>
    <string name="ov_section9_content3">You agree that your comments will not violate any right of any third-party, including copyright, trademark, privacy, personality or other personal or proprietary right. You further agree that your comments will not contain libelous or otherwise unlawful, abusive or obscene material, or contain any computer virus or other malware that could in any way affect the operation of the Service or any related Application. You may not use a false e-mail address, pretend to be someone other than yourself, or otherwise mislead us or third-parties as to the origin of any comments. You are solely responsible for any comments you make and their accuracy. We take no responsibility and assume no liability for any comments posted by you or any third-party.</string>
    <string name="ov_section10">SECTION 10 - PERSONAL INFORMATION</string>
    <string name="ov_section10_content1">Your submission of personal information through the store is governed by our Privacy Policy. To view our Privacy Policy.</string>
    <string name="ov_section11">SECTION 11 - ERRORS, INACCURACIES AND OMISSIONS</string>
    <string name="ov_section11_content1">Occasionally there may be information on our Application or in the Service that contains typographical errors, inaccuracies or omissions that may relate to product descriptions, pricing, promotions, offers, product shipping charges, transit times and availability. We reserve the right to correct any errors, inaccuracies or omissions, and to change or update information or cancel orders if any information in the Service or on any related Application is inaccurate at any time without prior notice (including after you have submitted your order).</string>
    <string name="ov_section11_content2">We undertake no obligation to update, amend or clarify information in the Service or on any related Application, including without limitation, pricing information, except as required by law. No specified update or refresh date applied in the Service or on any related Application, should be taken to indicate that all information in the Service or on any related Application has been modified or updated.</string>
    <string name="ov_section12">SECTION 12 - PROHIBITED USES</string>
    <string name="ov_section12_content1">In addition to other prohibitions as set forth in the Terms of Service, you are prohibited from using the Application or its content: (a) for any unlawful purpose; (b) to solicit others to perform or participate in any unlawful acts; © to violate any international, federal, provincial or state regulations, rules, laws, or local ordinances; (d) to infringe upon or violate our intellectual property rights or the intellectual property rights of others; (e) to harass, abuse, insult, harm, defame, slander, disparage, intimidate, or discriminate based on gender, sexual orientation, religion, ethnicity, race, age, national origin, or disability; (f) to submit false or misleading information;(g) to upload or transmit viruses or any other type of malicious code that will or may be used in any way that will affect the functionality or operation of the Service or of any related Application, other Applications, or the Internet; (h) to collect or track the personal information of others; (i) to spam, phish, pharm, pretext, spider, crawl, or scrape; (j) for any obscene or immoral purpose; or (k) to interfere with or circumvent the security features of the Service or any related Application, other Applications, or the Internet. We reserve the right to terminate your use of the Service or any related Application for violating any of the prohibited uses.</string>
    <string name="ov_section13">SECTION 13 - DISCLAIMER OF WARRANTIES; LIMITATION OF LIABILITY</string>
    <string name="ov_section13_content1">We do not guarantee, represent or warrant that your use of our service will be uninterrupted, timely, secure or error-free. We do not warrant that the results that may be obtained from the use of the service will be accurate or reliable.</string>
    <string name="ov_section13_content2">You agree that from time to time we may remove the service for indefinite periods of time or cancel the service at any time, without notice to you.You expressly agree that your use of, or inability to use, the service is at your sole risk. The service and all products and services delivered to you through the service are (except as expressly stated by us) provided \'as is\' and \'as available\' for your use, without any representation, warranties or conditions of any kind, either express or implied, including all implied warranties or conditions of merchantability, merchantable quality, fitness for a particular purpose, durability, title, and non-infringement.</string>
    <string name="ov_section13_content3">In no case shall Arraykart Techable Private Limited, our directors, officers, employees, affiliates, agents, contractors, interns, suppliers, service providers or licensors be liable for any injury, loss, claim, or any direct, indirect, incidental, punitive, special, or consequential damages of any kind, including, without limitation lost profits, lost revenue, lost savings, loss of data, replacement costs, or any similar damages, whether based in contract, tort (including negligence), strict liability or otherwise, arising from your use of any of the service or any products procured using the service, or for any other claim related in any way to your use of the service or any product, including, but not limited to, any errors or omissions in any content, or any loss or damage of any kind incurred as a result of the use of the service or any content (or product) posted, transmitted, or otherwise made available via the service, even if advised of their possibility.</string>
    <string name="ov_section13_content4">Because some states or jurisdictions do not allow the exclusion or the limitation of liability for consequential or incidental damages, in such states or jurisdictions, our liability shall be limited to the maximum extent permitted by law.</string>
    <string name="ov_section14">SECTION 14 - INDEMNIFICATION</string>
    <string name="ov_section14_content1">You agree to indemnify, defend and hold harmless Arraykart Techable Private Limited and our parent, subsidiaries, affiliates, partners, officers, directors, agents, contractors, licensors, service providers, subcontractors, suppliers, interns and employees, harmless from any claim or demand, including reasonable attorneys’ fees, made by any third-party due to or arising out of your breach of these Terms of Service or the documents they incorporate by reference, or your violation of any law or the rights of a third-party.</string>
    <string name="ov_section15">SECTION 15 - SEVERABILITY</string>
    <string name="ov_section15_content1">In the event that any provision of these Terms of Service is determined to be unlawful, void or unenforceable, such provision shall nonetheless be enforceable to the fullest extent permitted by applicable law, and the unenforceable portion shall be deemed to be severed from these Terms of Service, such determination shall not affect the validity and enforceability of any other remaining provisions.</string>
    <string name="ov_section16">SECTION 16 - TERMINATION</string>
    <string name="ov_section16_content1">The obligations and liabilities of the parties incurred prior to the termination date shall survive the termination of this agreement for all purposes.</string>
    <string name="ov_section16_content2">These Terms of Service are effective unless and until terminated by either you or us. You may terminate these Terms of Service at any time by notifying us that you no longer wish to use our Services, or when you cease using our Application.</string>
    <string name="ov_section16_content3">If in our sole judgment you fail, or we suspect that you have failed, to comply with any term or provision of these Terms of Service, we also may terminate this agreement at any time without notice and you will remain liable for all amounts due up to and including the date of termination; and/or accordingly may deny you access to our Services (or any part thereof).</string>
    <string name="ov_section17">SECTION 17 - ENTIRE AGREEMENT</string>
    <string name="ov_section17_content1">The failure of us to exercise or enforce any right or provision of these Terms of Service shall not constitute a waiver of such right or provision.</string>
    <string name="ov_section17_content2">These Terms of Service and any policies or operating rules posted by us on this Application or in respect to The Service constitutes the entire agreement and understanding between you and us and govern your use of the Service, superseding any prior or contemporaneous agreements, communications and proposals, whether oral or written, between you and us (including, but not limited to, any prior versions of the Terms of Service).</string>
    <string name="ov_section17_content3">Any ambiguities in the interpretation of these Terms of Service shall not be construed against the drafting party.</string>
    <string name="ov_section18">SECTION 18 - GOVERNING LAW</string>
    <string name="ov_section18_content1">These Terms of Service and any separate agreements whereby we provide you Services shall be governed by and construed in accordance with the laws of State and Central governments, India.</string>
    <string name="ov_section19">SECTION 19 - CHANGES TO TERMS OF SERVICE</string>
    <string name="ov_section19_content1">You can review the most current version of the Terms of Service at any time at this page. We reserve the right, at our sole discretion, to update, change or replace any part of these Terms of Service by posting updates and changes to our Application. It is your responsibility to check our Application periodically for changes. Your continued use of or access to our Application or the Service following the posting of any changes to these Terms of Service constitutes acceptance of those changes.</string>
    <string name="ov_section20">SECTION 20 - CONTACT INFORMATION</string>
    <string name="ov_section20_content1">Questions about the Terms of Service should be sent to us at yourfriends@arraykart.com</string>
    <string name="my_address">My Address</string>
    <string name="select_your_address">Select Your Address</string>
    <string name="my_orders">My Orders</string>
    <string name="my_cart">My Cart</string>
    <string name="notifications">Notifications</string>
    <string name="order_details">Order Details</string>
    <string name="order_placed">Your order has been placed</string>
    <string name="order_number">no.3654828234</string>
    <string name="product_name">product name</string>
    <string name="order_placed_price">RS. 500/—</string>
    <string name="order_placed_quantity">X 1</string>
    <string name="continue_shopping">Continue Shopping</string>
    <string name="pp_android_arraykart">This Privacy Policy applies to the Arraykart Android Application</string>
    <string name="pp_para1">Arraykart recognizes the importance of maintaining your privacy. We value your privacy and appreciate your trust in us. This Policy describes how we treat user information we collect on Arraykart Android Application and other offline sources. This Privacy Policy applies to current and former users of our Application and to our online customers. By visiting and/or using our application, you agree to this Privacy Policy</string>
    <string name="pp_para2">Arraykart App is a property of Arraykart Techable Private Limited, an Indian Company registered under the Companies Act, 2013 having its registered office at B-133 UGF, Nanhey Park, Uttam Nagar, New Delhi, Delhi - 110 059.</string>
    <string name="pp_contact_info">Contact information. We might collect your name, email, mobile number, phone number, street, city, state, Pincode, country, and IP address</string>
    <string name="pp_billing_payment">Payment and billing information. We might collect your billing name, billing address and payment method when you buy a ticket. We NEVER collect your credit card number or credit card expiry date or other details pertaining to your credit card on our Application. Credit card information will be obtained and processed by our online payment partner CC Avenue.</string>
    <string name="pp_info_you_post">Information you post. We collect the information you post in a public space on our Application or on a third-party social media Application belonging to Arraykart.</string>
    <string name="pp_demographic_info">Demographic information. We may collect demographic information about you, events you like, events you intend to participate in, tickets you buy, or any other information provided by you during the use of our Application. We might collect this as a part of a survey also.</string>
    <string name="pp_other_info">Other information. If you use our Application, we may collect information about your IP address and the browser you\'re using. We might look at what Application you came from, duration of time spent on our Application, pages accessed or what Application you visit when you leave us. We might also collect the type of mobile device you are using, or the version of the operating system your computer or device is running.</string>
    <string name="pp_info_collect1">We collect information in different ways</string>
    <string name="pp_info_collect2">We collect information directly from you. We collect information directly from you when you register for an event or buy tickets. We also collect information if you post a comment on our Applications or ask us a question through phone or email.</string>
    <string name="pp_info_collect3">We collect information from you passively. We use tracking tools like Google Analytics, Google Webmaster, browser cookies and web beacons for collecting information about your usage of our Application.</string>
    <string name="pp_info_collect4">We get information about you from third parties. For example, if you use an integrated social media feature on our Applications. The third-party social media Application will give us certain information about you. This could include your name and email address.</string>
    <string name="pp_info_use">Use of your personal information</string>
    <string name="pp_info_use1">We use information to contact you: We might use the information you provide to contact you for confirmation of a purchase on our Application or for other promotional purposes.</string>
    <string name="pp_info_use2">We use information to respond to your requests or questions. We might use your information to confirm your registration for an event or contest.</string>
    <string name="pp_info_use3">We use information to improve our products and services. We might use your information to customize your experience with us. This could include displaying content based upon your preferences.</string>
    <string name="pp_info_use4">We use information to look at Application trends and customer interests. We may use your information to make our Application and products better. We may combine information we get from you with information about you we get from third parties.</string>
    <string name="pp_info_use5">We use information for security purposes. We may use information to protect our company, our customers, or our Applications.</string>
    <string name="pp_info_use6">We use information for marketing purposes. We might send you information about special promotions or offers. We might also tell you about new features or products. These might be our own offers or products, or third-party offers or products we think you might find interesting. Or, for example, if you buy tickets from us we\'ll enroll you in our newsletter.</string>
    <string name="pp_info_use7">We use information to send you transactional communications. We might send you emails or SMS about your account or a ticket purchase.</string>
    <string name="pp_info_use8">We use information as otherwise permitted by law.</string>
    <string name="pp_info_share">Sharing of information with third-parties</string>
    <string name="pp_info_share1">We will share information with third parties who perform services on our behalf. We share information with vendors who help us manage our online registration process or payment processors or transactional message processors. Some vendors may be located outside of India.</string>
    <string name="pp_info_share2">We will share information with the event organizers. We share your information with event organizers and other parties responsible for fulfilling the purchase obligation. The event organizers and other parties may use the information we give them as described in their privacy policies.</string>
    <string name="pp_info_share3">We will share information with our business partners. This includes a third party who provide or sponsor an event, or who operates a venue where we hold events. Our partners use the information we give them as described in their privacy policies.</string>
    <string name="pp_info_share4">We may share information if we think we have to in order to comply with the law or to protect ourselves. We will share information to respond to a court order or subpoena. We may also share it if a government agency or investigatory body requests. Or, we might also share information when we are investigating potential fraud.</string>
    <string name="pp_info_share5">We may share information with any successor to all or part of our business. For example, if part of our business is sold we may give our customer list as part of that transaction.</string>
    <string name="pp_info_share6">We may share your information for reasons not described in this policy. We will tell you before we do this.</string>
    <string name="pp_email_opt_out">Email Opt-Out</string>
    <string name="pp_email_opt_out1">You can opt out of receiving our marketing emails. To stop receiving our promotional emails, please email unsubscriber@arraykart.com. It may take about ten days to process your request. Even if you opt out of getting marketing messages, we will still be sending you transactional messages through email and SMS about your purchases.</string>
    <string name="pp_third_party_apps">Third party Applications</string>
    <string name="pp_third_party_apps1">If you click on one of the links to third party Applications, you may be taken to Applications we do not control. This policy does not apply to the privacy practices of those Applications. Read the privacy policy of other Applications carefully. We are not responsible for these third-party Applications.</string>
    <string name="pp_change1">This Privacy Policy was last updated on 28.02.2022. From time to time we may change our privacy practices. We will notify you of any material changes to this policy as required by law. We will also post an updated copy on our Application. Please check our Application periodically for updates.</string>
    <string name="pp_change">Updates to this policy</string>
    <string name="pp_jurisdiction">Jurisdiction</string>
    <string name="pp_jurisdiction1">If you choose to visit the Application, your visit and any dispute over privacy is subject to this Policy and the Application\'s terms of use. In addition to the foregoing, any disputes arising under this Policy shall be governed by the laws of India.</string>
    <string name="pp_queries">If you have any questions about this Policy or other privacy concerns, you can also email us at yourfriends@arraykart.com</string>
    <string name="product_details">Product Details</string>
    <string name="add_to_cart">ADD TO CART</string>
    <string name="go_to_cart">Go to cart</string>
    <string name="buy_now">BUY NOW</string>
    <string name="place_order">Place Order</string>
    <string name="product_all_details">Product All Details</string>
    <string name="technical_name">technical_name</string>
    <string name="nutrient_efficiency_optimizer">Nutrient Efficiency Optimizer</string>
    <string name="description">description</string>
    <string name="description_detail">Epicel is highly active and safe.It increases the fertilizer efficiency and also mobilizes the nutrients present in the soil which are not available to the plants at normal course. Epicel is non-phytotoxic.</string>
    <string name="target_disease">target_disease</string>
    <string name="na">NA</string>
    <string name="target_field_crops">target_field_crops</string>
    <string name="target_field_crop_name">Raddish</string>
    <string name="target_vegetable_crops">target_vegetable_crops</string>
    <string name="target_vegetable_crop_name">Garlic</string>
    <string name="target_fruit_crops">target_fruit_crops</string>
    <string name="target_fruit_crop_name">Grapes, Guava, Sapota, Citrus, Mango, Pomegranate, Custard Apple, Banana. Apple, Coconut etc.</string>
    <string name="target_plantation_crops">target_plantation_crops</string>
    <string name="target_plantation_crop_name">Cardamom. Tea, Coffee, Floriculture. Home gardening, Medicinal plants etc.</string>
    <string name="mode_of_action">mode_of_action</string>
    <string name="mode_of_action_detail">Epicel™ is highly active and safe. It increases the fertilizer efficiency and also mobilizes the nutrients present in the soil which are not available to the plants at normal course..</string>
    <string name="duration_of_effect">duration_of_effect</string>
    <string name="compatability_with_other_chemicals">compatability_with_other_chemicals</string>
    <string name="compatability_with_other_chemicals_detail">Epicel is compatible with all agriculture inputs</string>
    <string name="frequency_of_application">frequency_of_application</string>
    <string name="frequency_of_application_no">Two</string>
    <string name="dosage">dosage</string>
    <string name="dosage_detail">Apply 2.5kg per hectare of . . to apply 1 tonne per hectare stabilized organic manure at the time of Land preparation</string>
    <string name="water_requirement">water_requirement (ltr)</string>
    <string name="time_of_application">time_of_application</string>
    <string name="time_of_application_detail">After one month of sowing or after three weeks of transplantation, second application is recommended as per requirement and duration of the crop.</string>
    <string name="method_of_application">method_of_application</string>
    <string name="method_of_application_detail">Through drip irrigation or through drenching.</string>
    <string name="waiting_period">waiting_period</string>
    <string name="label_on_product">label_on_product</string>
    <string name="storage">storage</string>
    <string name="storage_detail">Store in dry and cool place. avoid direct sunlight</string>
    <string name="country_of_origin">country_of_origin</string>
    <string name="country_of_origin_value">India</string>
    <string name="shelf_life">shelf_life</string>
    <string name="shelf_life_detail">Two years from the date of manufacturing in original sealed pack</string>
    <string name="volume">volume</string>
    <string name="volume_value">1Kg,5Kg</string>
    <string name="dimensions">dimensions</string>
    <string name="dimensions_value">15x10x4</string>
    <string name="state1">state(solid/liquid)</string>
    <string name="state_value">solid</string>
    <string name="category">category</string>
    <string name="category_value">Growth Enhancers</string>
    <string name="inventory_id">inventory_id</string>
    <string name="inventory_id_value">1234</string>
    <string name="brand">brand</string>
    <string name="brand_value">Excel Industries Ltd.</string>
    <string name="edit_your_profile">Edit Your Profile</string>
    <string name="first_name">First Name*</string>
    <string name="last_name">Last Name*</string>
    <string name="contact">Contact*</string>
    <string name="email">Email*</string>
    <string name="save">Save</string>
    <string name="ratings_reviews"><![CDATA[Ratings & Reviews]]></string>
    <string name="_0_0">0.0</string>
    <string name="no_ratings_yet">no ratings yet</string>
    <string name="no_review_yet">no Review yet</string>
    <string name="return_policy">Return Policy</string>
    <string name="returns">RETURNS</string>
    <string name="return_policy_description1">Our policy lasts 7 days. If 7 days have gone by since your purchase, unfortunately, we can’t offer you a refund or exchange.</string>
    <string name="return_policy_description2">To be eligible for a return, your item must be unused and in the same condition that you received it. It must also be in the original packaging.</string>
    <string name="return_policy_description3">To return Seeds, Fertilizers, Pesticides, Adjuvants, Crop Nutrition, and Farm Machinery, the packet should not be opened. The product should be in clean condition while returning or exchanging.</string>
    <string name="return_policy_description4">To complete your return, we require a receipt or proof of purchase.</string>
    <string name="refunds">Refunds (if applicable)</string>
    <string name="refund_description1">Once your return is received and inspected, we will send you an email or update on your profile to notify you that we have received your returned item. We will also notify you of the approval or rejection of your refund.</string>
    <string name="refund_description2">If it is approved, then your refund will be processed, and a credit will automatically be applied to your credit/debit card or original method of payment, within a certain amount of days. For Cash on Delivery payment, the customer has to give his/her Bank Account number to process the refund.</string>
    <string name="late_refund">Late or missing refunds (if applicable)</string>
    <string name="late_refund_content1">If you haven’t received a refund yet, first check your bank account again.</string>
    <string name="late_refund_content2">Then contact your credit/debit card company, it may take some time before your refund is officially posted.</string>
    <string name="late_refund_content3">Next, contact your bank. There is often some processing time before a refund is posted.</string>
    <string name="late_refund_content4">If you’ve done all of this and you still have not received your refund yet, please contact us at yourfriends@arraykart.com.</string>
    <string name="sale_items">Sale items (if applicable)</string>
    <string name="sale_items_content1">Only regular-priced items may be refunded, unfortunately, sale items cannot be refunded.</string>
    <string name="exchanges">Exchanges (if applicable)</string>
    <string name="exchange_content1">We only replace items if they are defective or damaged. If you need to exchange it for the same item, make a request through purchase history at our application or send us an email at yourfriends@arraykart.com. Your product will be exchanged from the given address on certain days.</string>
    <string name="shipping">Shipping</string>
    <string name="shipping_content1">To return your product, you should request it on our application. Our Delivery boy will pick up the product from you after going through the Quality checks. If we find the product the same as delivered to you, we will initiate your refund. The amount will be deposited into your Bank Account on certain days.</string>
    <string name="shipping_content2">Depending on where you live, the time it may take for your exchanged product to reach you may vary.</string>
    <string name="search_arraykart_com">Search Arraykart.com</string>
    <string name="trending">Trending</string>
    <string name="new_arrival">New Arrival</string>
    <string name="best_selling">Best Selling</string>
    <string name="sort_by_cost">Sort By Cost</string>
    <string name="low_to_high">Low to High</string>
    <string name="high_to_low">High to Low</string>
    <string name="user_name">User name</string>
    <string name="email_id">Email id</string>
    <string name="my_wishlist">My WishList</string>
    <string name="_5">5</string>
    <string name="worth_every_penny">worth every penny</string>
    <string name="product_detail">write about products in details</string>
    <string name="sachin_jha">sachin jha</string>
    <string name="noida">noida</string>
    <string name="certified_buyer">Certified Buyer</string>
    <string name="more">more</string>
    <string name="jan_2021">Jan,2021</string>
    <string name="less">less</string>
    <string name="terms_conditions"><![CDATA[Terms & Conditions]]></string>
    <string name="faq">Frequently Asked Questions</string>
    <string name="faq1">1. What is the Offer?</string>
    <string name="ans1">*The Offer is flat 100 Rs. Instant Discount on a range of products sold on Flipkart Platform upon paying through ‘Flipkart Pay Later’ for the first time (only available to customers of Flipkart Pay Later’ product) also known as “Buy Now Pay Later” from 01st December 2021 00:00 hrs to 20th December 2021 23:59 hrs. Minimum order value is Rs. 500.</string>
    <string name="reason_for_cancel">please let us know the reason ??</string>
    <string name="reason1">reason number 1 !!</string>
    <string name="insecticides_most_important">Insecticides most important</string>
    <string name="free_coupons">Free coupons</string>
    <string name="rs_40000">RS.40000/-</string>
    <string name="rs_50000">RS.50000/-</string>
    <string name="offer_applied">Offer applied</string>
    <string name="coupon_applied">Coupon applied</string>
    <string name="quantity">QTY:</string>
    <string name="_1">1</string>
    <string name="add_to_wishlist">Add to WishList</string>
    <string name="remove_item">Remove item</string>
    <string name="price_detail">Price Detail</string>
    <string name="price_2items">Price (2items)</string>
    <string name="delivery">Delivery</string>
    <string name="free">Free</string>
    <string name="best_deals">Best Deals</string>
    <string name="products">Products</string>
    <string name="tag_line">We help you connect to the world!</string>
    <string name="head_title">Head Title</string>
    <string name="textview">TextView</string>
    <string name="rose">rose</string>
    <string name="price">Price</string>
    <string name="rate">rate</string>
    <string name="new1">new</string>
    <string name="all_products">All Products</string>
    <string name="namaskaar">Namaskaar!</string>
    <string name="category_name">Category name</string>
    <string name="sachin">sachin</string>
    <string name="rs">Rs.---/-</string>
    <string name="qty_1">Qty: 1</string>
    <string name="_2kg">2kg</string>
    <string name="mon_12th_dec_2021_12_24">Mon,12th dec 2021 12:24</string>
    <string name="order_has_been_placed_succesfully">order has been placed succesfully</string>
    <string name="tus_13th_dec_2021_9_45">Tus,13th dec 2021 9:45</string>
    <string name="order_packed">order packed</string>
    <string name="order_has_been_packed">order has been packed</string>
    <string name="order_shipped">order shipped</string>
    <string name="wed_14th_dec_2021_10_40">Wed,14Th dec 2021 10:40</string>
    <string name="order_has_been_shipped_succesfully">order has been shipped succesfully</string>
    <string name="order_delivered">order delivered</string>
    <string name="wed_15th_dec_2021_9_43">Wed,15th dec 2021 9:43</string>
    <string name="order_delivered_on_time">order delivered on time</string>
    <string name="your_rating">Your Rating</string>
    <string name="cancel_your_order">Cancel your order</string>
    <string name="return_your_order">Return your order</string>
    <string name="delivered_on_sunday_28_11_2021">Delivered on sunday 28/11/2021</string>
    <string name="rate_and_review">Rate and Review</string>
    <string name="cash_on_delivery">CASH ON DELIVERY</string>
    <string name="cash_on_delivery1">Pay when your order arrives at home</string>
    <string name="_4_5">4.5</string>
    <string name="_150_ratings">150 ratings</string>
    <string name="special_price">special price</string>
    <string name="Rs">₹___</string>
    <string name="Rs1">₹</string>
    <string name="___">___</string>
    <string name="_20_off">20% off</string>
    <string name="offers_and_coupons">Offers and Coupons</string>
    <string name="discount">Special PriceGet extra 14% off (price inclusive of discount)</string>
    <string name="offer">Bank OfferFlat ₹100 off on first Flipkart Pay Later order of ₹500 and above</string>
    <string name="indian_rupee_symbol">The Indian rupee sign (₹) is the currency symbol for the Indian rupee, the official currency of India. Designed by Udaya Kumar, it was presented to the public by the Government of India on 15 July 2010, following its selection through an open competition among Indian residents. The Indian rupee sign (₹) is the currency symbol for the Indian rupee, the official currency of India. Designed by Udaya Kumar, it was presented to the public by the Government of India on 15 July 2010, following its selection through an open competition among Indian residents. The Indian rupee sign (₹) is the currency symbol for the Indian rupee, the official currency of India. Designed by Udaya Kumar, it was presented to the public by the Government of India on 15 July 2010, following its selection through an open competition among Indian residents. The Indian rupee sign (₹) is the currency symbol for the Indian rupee, the official currency of India. Designed by Udaya Kumar, it was presented to the public by the Government of India on 15 July 2010, following its selection through an open competition among Indian residents.</string>
    <string name="click_for_more_details">Click for More Details</string>
    <string name="click_for_more_review">Click for more review</string>
    <string name="suggested_products">Suggested Products</string>
    <string name="placegallery">PlaceGallery</string>
    <string name="_20000">20000</string>
    <string name="main_title">Main Title</string>
    <string name="qty">QTY :</string>
    <string name="add_quality_of_products">Add Quality of Products</string>
    <string name="product_enjoyed">We hope you enjoyed your product with us today</string>
    <string name="awesome_i_love_it">Awesome. I love it</string>
    <string name="tell_us_what_you_loved">Tell us what you loved</string>
    <string name="send_feedback">Send feedback</string>
    <string name="address">Address</string>
    <string name="edit">Edit</string>
    <string name="remove">Remove</string>
    <string name="recent_searches">Recent Searches</string>
    <string name="price_of_products">Price of products</string>
    <string name="rs_value_end">/-</string>
    <string name="notification_preferences">Notification Preferences</string>
    <string name="account_setting">Account Setting</string>
    <string name="logout_of_this_app">Logout of this app</string>
    <string name="logout_of_all_devices">Logout of all devices</string>
    <string name="shipping_detail">SHIPPING DETAIL</string>
    <string name="full_name">FULL NAME</string>
    <string name="full_address">Full address</string>
    <string name="change_your_address">Change your address</string>
    <string name="sign_in">Sign in</string>
    <string name="use_number">Use Number</string>
    <string name="enter_otp">Enter Otp</string>
    <string name="resend">Resend</string>
    <string name="options_for_sign_up">Options for sign up</string>
    <string name="view_your_wishlist">View Your WishList</string>
    <string name="free_offer">free offer</string>
    <string name="rs_499999">Rs.499999/-</string>
    <string name="rs_599999">RS.599999/-</string>
    <string name="cash_on_delivery_available">Cash on delivery available</string>
    <string name="product_name_here">Product Name Here</string>
    <string name="sign_up">Sign Up</string>
    <string name="submit">Submit</string>
</resources>